allen-heath.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Statement - Allen & Heath

###  1 Introduction

1.1 This website ("Website") belongs to Allen & Heath Limited. Allen & Heath Limited is the data controller within the meaning of the UK Data Protection Act. Allen & Heath recognizes privacy and security as being a concern for individuals accessing the internet. Even when you're just browsing our Website, we want to make you comfortable with our privacy practices and the security measures we take to protect your personal information. Personal information is data that can be used to uniquely identify or contact an individual.

1.2 With this privacy statement ("Statement") we inform you on Allen & Heath's privacy practices and security measures concerning your personal information collected during your use of this Website, including the service to download software for your Allen & Heath device (the "Service").

1.3 If we decide to change our Statement, such changes will be posted here on this Website, so please check back periodically to ensure you have the most current Statement.

### 2 What personal information is collected?

2.1 When you use this Website, we (or third parties engaged by us to that purpose) may request you to fill in personal information, including your name and e-mail address. We require this information if you wish to use the Service.

2.2 Furthermore, we may process your IP address, browser specifications, Internet service provider, referring and exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp and click stream data. This information is aggregated to measure number of visits, average time spent on this Website, pages viewed, etc. We use this information to analyze and measure the use of our Website and to improve the content thereof.

2.3 We may also use cookies to register your preferences and visits to this Website. A cookie is a small text file that is stored on your computer. At your next visit to this Website, your computer sends the information from that file back to us. You can change your browser settings as to reject all or certain cookies, or to be informed of every new cookie. If cookies are not accepted, it is possible that you are unable to use (parts of) this Website and/or the Service.

### 3 Who has access to the information?

3.1 We may instruct third parties to perform services on our behalf in respect of the processing of your personal data. We will not disclose your personal information to any other third party unless we believe that disclosure is necessary: (a) in order to conform to legal requirements; or (b) to enforce this Statement and the terms and conditions of this Website. We may disclose your personal information to the approved Allen & Heath distributor/s in your county if you have expressly granted permission for us to do so.

### 4 How is your information used?

4.1 Allen & Heath's primary goal in collecting personal information is to enable you to use the Service, and to enable us to contact you to confirm the receipt of your download order or if a problem arises. If you have permitted us to do so, we will also use your e-mail address to send you information on our products and services ("Mailing").

4.2 Allen & Heath may undertake research on our users' demographics, interests, etc. from our server log files. We do this to better understand and serve our users. This research is compiled and analyzed on an aggregated basis so as to prevent identification of personal information relating to an individual.

### 5 Security measures

5.1 No data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, Allen & Heath Limited cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from our Website, and therefore you use our Website at your own risk. Once we receive your personal information, we use our best effort to ensure its security on our systems, to protect it against loss, misuse or alteration.

5.2 When you give Allen & Heath Limited personal information, that information may be electronically sent to servers outside of the country where you originally entered the information. In addition, that information may be used, stored and/or processed outside of the country where you entered that information. Whenever Allen & Heath Limited (or a third party engaged by us to that purpose) handles personal information, regardless of where this occurs, it takes steps to ensure that your information is treated securely and in accordance with the relevant Terms and Conditions and this Statement.

### 6 Review and deregister

6.1 If you would like to review, correct or change any personal information you have provided, please contact us by using the e-mail address mentioned below. If you receive Mailings, and you no longer want to, you can deregister by using the unsubscribe link in each Mailing.

### 7 Inquiries

7.1 For further information or complaints please contact us at the e-mail address or the business address mentioned below.

Business address:

Allen & Heath Limited  
Kernick Industrial Estate  
Penryn  
Cornwall  
TR10 9LU  
United Kingdom

Tel. +44 (0)1326 372070

E-mail address: marketing@allen-heath.com

VAT number: 876333694

We use cookies to give you the best possible experience on our site. By continuing to use the site you agree to our use of cookies.Accept Find out more
